nissanfinance.com 2018-08-23

# NMAC Finance Account Manager

## Privacy

##### We value your Privacy

##### Nissan Motor Acceptance collects information from our users at several different points on our website. Nissan Motor Acceptance Corporation ( **NMAC** or **Nissan** ) is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or rent this information to others. We will only share this information with our affiliates, retailers, joint marketing partners and vendors contracted to do business on our behalf as permitted by law. NMAC uses two types of user information: anonymous information gathered from cookies and log files, and personal information you provide us for certain services. See below for definitions of each of these methods. If you provide your social security number to us, we will (1) protect the confidentiality of social security numbers, (2) prohibit unlawful disclosure of social security numbers, and (3) limit access to social security numbers. 

##### NMAC Privacy Policy

##### Please use the links below to download a PDF version of the policy.

**_  
**Privacy Notice Frequently Asked Questions**  
_**

Effective December 21, 2013.

**Anonymous Information and Online Tracking**

NMAC does not track your online activities outside of this website nor do we allow any other party to track your website activities through this site. We do use cookies to identify you within this site, as described below. If your browser is set for "Do Not Track", you may use this site but may have limited access to some features, as described below.

**Cookies and Log Files** : A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to personal information, until a user provides that information (see below). If a user rejects or deletes the cookie, he/she may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to receive notification of special offers, or participate in any contests that may take place. Cookies also enable us to track and aggregate clickstream behavior data. By doing this we can better target the interests of our users and enhance their experience on our site. Nissan also maintains standard web logs that record data about all visitors to this website. These logs may contain: 

•The internet domain from which you access this site.  
•Your IP address : your computer is automatically assigned an IP address when you surf the internet. Your IP address is either static or dynamic. A static IP address may be identifiable to you; a dynamic address is usually not identifiable to you.  
•The type of browser and operating system you use.  
•The date and time you visited this site.  
•The pages you viewed on this site.  
•The address of the website from which you linked.

Nissan uses web log and clickstream information to help us design our site, to identify popular site features and to make the site more useful for visitors. Web logs are recorded in sequential files, and we normally do not attempt to identify individuals from these logs. However, we may use web logs to identify persons attempting to break into, disrupt, or damage our site. We may share web log information with law enforcement personnel if we believe evidence exists, of a violation or intended violation of federal, state or local laws and regulations.

Nissan advertising at other non-Nissan sites may be serviced by Nissan service providers, who may use cookies to collect information about your visits to those sites. Information collected may include the pages visited, date and time, browser information and/or IP address. We normally make no attempt to link this information to you personally, except under circumstances described above. This information is gathered in order to help us customize and target our advertising to the needs and interests of our customers.

**Volunteering Personal Information**

Users may choose to volunteer personal information (name, e-mail address, phone number, etc. ) in order for us to provide them with services such as brochure and information requests, surveys and contests, site announcements, and special offers at the time of the request or in the future. Nissan does not sell or rent user information to any third parties. We share user information with our affiliates, retailers, joint marketing partners and vendors contracted to do business on our behalf . When the user signs up for certain services and offers on our site, we will share names, or other contact information necessary for any associate third party to provide these services. Nissan will share user information in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is collected.

**Security**

Nissan takes all reasonable precautions to protect our users' information, both while the information is being transmitted and after it is received by us. Furthermore, once the information has been received by us, we use security procedures and policies that commensurate with industry standards to safeguard against loss, theft, unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification and disclosure.

**Links**

This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Nissan Motor Acceptance Corporation is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each website that collects personal information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Notifications of Changes**

We retain the right to change this privacy policy at any time. We will post those changes to this page so that users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will use, share, and disclose all information in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time the information was collected.

**Certain Disclosures**

Nissan may disclose any data, whether personally identifiable or not, to any person performing audit, legal, operational or other similar services for Nissan. Whenever possible, we will require any recipient of personal information for these purposes to agree in writing to hold the information in confidence, to use the information only for the permitted purpose, and to return or destroy the information when the services are completed. We may also disclose any data, whether personally identifiable or not, when required to do so by subpoena, court order, or warrant. Whenever feasible, Nissan will notify the effected user by e-mail that such disclosure will or has occurred . We may also disclose any data, whether personally identifiable or not, when we reasonably deem it necessary to protect the safety of (i) an individual, (ii) the public, or (iii) the security and reliability of Nissan and/or this website.

**Children**

Nissan does not knowingly allow anyone under the age of 13 to participate in any services offered on our website which requires the submission of user information. If we learn that a user is under 13 and has submitted user information to us, we will delete that information as promptly as possible.

Nissan Contact Information

To contact Nissan offline you can send mail to:  
Nissan Motor Acceptance Corporation  
Attn: Privacy Office  
P. O. Box 660360  
Dallas, TX 75063-0360  
Or during business hours, call 1-800-456- NMAC.
